# TREVOR JARVIS

FULL-STACK JAVASCRIPT DEVELOPER 

◆ SALT LAKE CITY, UT 

◆ 5037500089

### • DETAILS •

Salt Lake City, UT 5037500089 tmjarv@gmail.com

# • LINKS •

Portfolio Site

LinkedIn Profile

### • SKILLS •

JavaScript

HTML/CSS

React.js

Express.js

Node.js

SQL

Python

Swift

C

PostgreSQL

MongoDB

Firebase (Hosting, Auth, Databases)

Agile Project Management

**Product Management** 

Accounting

Finance

Sales Management

#### • LANGUAGES •

Spanish

Portuguese

### PROFILE

Software developer and startup executive specializing in Javascript and React, product and operations management, and client relations.

Working for small companies, I have worn every hat from sales and marketing to accounting and HR. I'm passionate about entrepreneurship and creating go-to-market strategies with a clear path to profitability. I've helped 15+ companies create technology-based solutions to fulfill customer needs.

#### EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

# Technical Project Manager at Standard Behavior LLC., Salt Lake City, UT

January 2020 — April 2020

Standard Behavior offers a full range of marketing services, and has recently expanded
into app development with the acquisition of App Raptors team members. In my role, I
was in charge of sales, onboarding, and management for development projects.

#### President, Product Manager at The Daily Shifts LLC., Provo, UT

August 2020 — August 2020

• The Daily Shifts is a new SaaS company with the mission to help customers reach their highest selves, and released its core iOS application in 2019. In this role, I oversaw the quality assurance aspects of the application and supervised the development team.

# Chief Executive Officer - Chief Operating Officer at App Raptors LLC., Provo, UT June 2018 — January 2020

- App Raptors was a software design and development firm that builds apps and websites
  for companies and new entrepreneurs. As CEO, I oversaw all customer-facing and
  internal/strategic operations of the company and led the company until joining the
  Standard Behavior team.
- Prior to my promotion to CEO, I served as Chief Operating Officer. I was in charge of day-to-day company operations. Responsibilities included sales, project management, recruiting, process design, and more.

## Company Administrator at App Raptors LLC., Provo, UT

March 2018 — June 2018

 Took charge of administrative functions of the business, including accounting, invoicing, payroll, project documentation, and more. Worked directly with company executives to prepare reports, create proposals, and assist in the sales process.

### Software Development Intern at Intel Corporation, Hillsboro, OR

September 2013 — July 2014

• Provided QC in a team of software engineers tasked to build enterprise reimbursement software for companies like Apple, HP, and Samsung.

#### EDUCATION

BS - Entrepreneurial Management, Brigham Young University, Provo, UT

September 2016 — December 2019

Repeated coursework in analysis, information systems, innovation, and marketing.